<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>
  <title>null</title>
  <link>https://blog.gdocweb.com/</link>
  <description>null</description>
  <item>
    <title>Introducing gdocweb</title>
    <link>https://blog.gdocweb.com/introducing-gdocweb.html</link>
     <description>gdocweb Blog December 28th, 2023   Yes. This post started off as a Google Docs document that you can see by clicking that link. I’m assuming you’re seeing it on the web which is where it’s supposed to be. It was translated to a web page seamlessly using gdocweb . Gdocweb converts Google Docs to websites or more importantly</description>
   </item>
  <item>
    <title>Blog Comments</title>
    <link>https://blog.gdocweb.com/blog-comments.html</link>
     <description>gdocweb Blog January 3rd, 2024   gdocweb draws its power from Google Docs. It also inherits some of the Google Docs limitations. One such limitation is the rigidness of the platform, a great example would be in blog comments. With most tools we can simply add a comment widget and end on a high note. However, Google Docs has</description>
   </item>
  <item>
    <title>Styling and Dark Mode</title>
    <link>https://blog.gdocweb.com/styling-and-dark-mode.html</link>
     <description>gdocweb Blog January 8th, 2024   When using Google Docs it’s often tempting to reach out to the font or color toolbar to design your document as you see fit. This would work great for simple sites but as gdocweb evolves you might find it produces a result that isn’t as attractive as you might want. The reason for</description>
   </item>
  <item>
    <title>gdocweb Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.gdocweb.com/index.html</link>
     <description>gdocweb Blog  January 8th, 2024   When using Google Docs it’s often tempting to reach out to the font or color toolbar to design your document as you see fit. This would work great for simple sites but as gdocweb evolves you might find it produces a result that isn’t as attractive as you might want. The reason</description>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
